Ivy Ledbetter Lee Papers, 1881-2003 (bulk 1915-1946): Finding Aid MC085
Public Policy Papers
- Series 7: Ivy Lee and Associates, 1910-1961; 92 boxes
  - Subseries 7D: Matter Sent Out (MSO), 1914-1947; 90 boxes
    - American Delegation at the London Naval Conference, 1930 March; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - American Foundation for the Blind, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - American Geographical Society, 1918; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - American Historical Association, 1929; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - American Hospital of Paris, 1920; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - American I.G. Chemical Corporation, 1929-1945; 2 folders (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
    - American Law Institute, 1930; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - American Legion National Executive Committee, 1919-1920; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - American Locomotive Company, 1931 September; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1919-1922; 2 boxes
      - 1919-1920, 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Bulletins, 1920; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - 1921-1922, 2 folders (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
    - American Railway Association, 1916-1917; 1 box
      - 1916-1917, 2 folders (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
      - Printed, 1916-1917; 1 folder (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - American Red Cross, 1917-1929; 2 boxes
      - 1917, 3 folders (Box 34, Folder 6-8)
      - 1917-1920, 4 folders (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
      - Printed, 1917-1920; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - 1928-1929, 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - American Shipbuilders, Committee of, 1920; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - American Shipping and Commerce Corporation, 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - American Smelting & Refining Company, 1921-1930; 2 boxes
      - 1923-1930, 1 folder (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - 1921-1922, 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Printed, 1921-1930; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors & Publishers (ASCAP), 1932-1934; 1 box
      - 1932-1934, 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Music Reports, 1934; 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1932-1934; 2 folders (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
    - Anglo American Oil Company, 1923, 1925and undated, 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - American Tobacco Company, 1928-1943; 4 boxes
      - 1928-1929, 1 folder (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - 1929-1932, 7 folders (Box 37, Folder 1-7)
      - 1933-1943, 5 folders (Box 38, Folder 1-5)
      - Printed, 1933-1943; 1 folder (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Newspaper Articles and Ads, 1928-1938; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Anaconda Copper Mining Company, 1923-1926; 1 folder (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Anthracite Operators, 1921-1926; 2 boxes
      - 1921-1926, 3 folders (Box 39, Folder 3-5)
      - Printed, 1921-1925; 2 folders (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
      - Printed, 1925-1926; 2 folders (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
      - Various Bulletins, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Various Bulletins, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Statements, 1923; 2 folders (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
    - Armour & Company, 1923-1935; 2 boxes
      - 1923-1934, 3 folders (Box 40, Folder 7-9)
      - Printed, 1923; 1 folder (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Printed, 1924-1935; 3 folders (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
    - Argentine-American Chamber of Commerce, 1924; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Associated Railroads of New Jersey, 1939; 1 box
      - 1939, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1939; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Assoc. for the Assistance of Crippled Children, 1939-1945; 2 boxes
      - 1940-1945, 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Printed, 1939-1941; 1 folder (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Printed, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Association of Railway Executives, 1919-1922; 2 boxes
      - 1919-1922, 11 folders (Box 42, Folder 2-12)
      - 1922, 3 folders (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
      - Printed, 1919-1922; 3 folders (Box 43, Folder 4-6)
      - "Railroad Information", 1920-1922; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - "The Railroad Inquiry", 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Avon Old Farms Preparatory School, 1927; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Bacardi Rum, 1936; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Bakelite Corporation, 1926-1928; 1 folder (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Bankers Trust, 1920-1927; 3 boxes
      - "Foreign Information", 1920-1921; 5 folders (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
      - "Foreign Information", 1922-1923; 5 folders (Box 45, Folder 1-5)
      - "Foreign Information", 1923-1924; 3 folders (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
      - Department of Research, 1920; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - "Bulletins", 1920-1922; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1921-1927; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Barber Asphalt Corporation, 1942-1946; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1916-1930; 3 boxes
      - 1916-1930, 3 folders (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
      - Printed, 1916-1930; 2 folders (Box 47, Folder 4-5)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1916; 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
      - Annual Conference, 1929-1930; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - "Bethlehem Review", 1924-1930; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Annual Reports, 1920-1928; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Government Proposals, 1916; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Bituminous Coal Institute, 1946; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Botany Worsted Mills, 1926-1929; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Boyce Thompson Insttitute, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Breed, William C, 1933; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Briggs Manufacturing Company, 1933-1946; 2 folders (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
    - Broadway Temple Building Corporation, 1924; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Brown University, 1945; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Buffalo & Lake Erie Traction Company, circa 1916; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Building Managers & Owners Association, 1929; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Calco Chemical Company, 1931; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Cambell, Starring, & Company, 1929; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Cardinal Mercier Testimonial, 1919; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Carnegie Corporation, Philanthropy, 1921; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Catholic Charities, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Catholic Club, 1946; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Cement Information Service, 1923-1925; 3 folders (Box 50, Folder 9-11)
    - Central Jersey Coal Company, 1922; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Chase National Bank, 1923; 1926; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Checker Cab Company, 1929; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Chemical National Bank, 1921-1924; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Chile Copper Company, 1922; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Chilean Nitrate of Soda, 1930-1945; 1 box
      - 1930-1931, 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - 1937-1945, 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Chilean Nitrate Educational Bureau, "Farm for Victory", 1942-1946; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Chrysler Corporation, 1929-1946; 6 boxes
      - 1929-1936, 6 folders (Box 51, Folder 2-7)
      - 1937-1940, 6 folders (Box 52, Folder 1-6)
      - 1940-1944, 9 folders (Box 53, Folder 1-9)
      - 1945-1946, 2 folders (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed, 1929-1936; 4 folders (Box 54, Folder 3-6)
      - Printed, 1937-1945; 7 folders (Box 55, Folder 1-7)
      - Printed, 1946; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Books, 1943-1946; 3 folders (Box 56, Folder 2-4)
    - Chrysler, Walter Jr, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - The Church Pension Fund, 1918-1930; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Citizens Committee to Obtain Justice for the Wounded, 1921; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Citizens Committee on the Control of Crime in New York, Inc, 1936-1937; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Colorado Fuel and Iron Company, 1915-1927; 1 box
      - 1915-1916, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - 1921, 1924, 1927, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Printed, 1915-1916; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1930-1946; 3 boxes
      - 1930, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - 1934-1946, 3 folders (Box 57, Folder 5-7)
      - Printed, 1934-1943; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
      - Printed, 1944-1946; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Annual Reports, 1938-1945; 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
      - "Talks", 1936-1939; 4 folders (Box 58, Folder 4-7)
      - "Talks", 1940-1946; 6 folders (Box 59, Folder 1-6)
      - "Listen", 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Commercial Investment Trust, 1926; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Commonwealth & Southern Corporation, 1935-1942; 2 boxes
      - 1935-1936, 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
      - 1937-1942, 3 folders (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
    - The Commonwealth Fund, 1927; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Continental Banking Company, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Copper & Brass Research Association, 1921-1931; 4 boxes
      - 1921-1923, 3 folders (Box 60, Folder 6-8)
      - 1924-1930, 4 folders (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
      - Bulletins, 1921-1927; 3 folders (Box 61, Folder 5-7)
      - Bulletins, 1928-1931; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - ads, 1924; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Printed, 1922-1929; 4 folders (Box 62, Folder 3-6)
      - Printed, 1930; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Corning Glass Works, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Cotton Textile Institute, 1926-1931; 4 boxes
      - 1926-1929, 3 folders (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
      - 1929-1930, 6 folders (Box 64, Folder 1-6)
      - 1930-1931, 4 folders (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
      - Printed, 1926-1929; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 5-7)
      - Printed, 1929-1931; 4 folders (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
      - "Letter of Information", 1927-1930; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Cotton Textile Merchants, Association of, 1926-1930; 2 boxes
      - 1926-1927, 2 folders (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
      - 1928-1929, 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed, 1927-1930; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - "Cotton Textile Bulletin", 1927-1928; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Cravath, Paul D, 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Cromwell, James H. R, 1928; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Detroit River Bridge, 1925; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Dillon Read & Company, 1927-1929; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Dobbs School Alumnae, 1919-1920; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Dominick & Dominick, 1924-1932; 3 boxes
      - 1925-1930, 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Bulletin, 1924-1925; 3 folders (Box 67, Folder 11-13)
      - Bulletin, 1926-1928; 6 folders (Box 68, Folder 1-6)
      - Bulletin, 1929-1932; 7 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-7)
    - Dreicher & Company, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Presidents Conference, 1923-1925; 1 box
      - 1923-1925, 4 folders (Box 70, Folder 1-4)
      - "Public Opinion on our Railroads", 1923; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Electric Ferries Inc, 1926-1930; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Electric Railways of New York State, 1917; 1 box
      - 1917, 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Printed, 1917; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Episcopal Church, 1918-1931; 1 box
      - Church War Commission, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Pension Fund, 1931; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Episcopal Theological School, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Equitable Trust Company, 1917; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Equity Corporation, 1936; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Fifth Avenue Coach Company, 1917; 1919; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library (Standard Oil Company), 1932; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson Rev., Sermons, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Fosdick, Raymond Blaine, 1918; 1922; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Frazier Jelke & Company, 1927-1929; 1 box
      - 1928-1929, 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - "Investment Surveys", 1927-1929; 2 folders (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
    - Freeport Texas Company, 1930; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - French Finanical Agency, 1920-1921; 2 folders (Box 71, Folder 14-15)
    - Frick Collection, 1935 December; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - General Asphalt Company, 1930; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - General Mills, 1928-1945; 3 folders (Box 72, Folder 2-4)
    - General Outdoor Advertising, 1925-1927; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - George L. Dyer Company, 1921; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Georgia Railway and Power Company, 1921-1922; 1 box
      - 1921-1922, 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - "Two Bells" and "Public Service", 1921; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - German Students Cooperative Association, 1925; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Gifts to Belgian Soldiers, 1918; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Gold Dust Company, 1925; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Goldman, Sachs & Company, 1924 December; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1936-1939; 2 boxes
      - 1936-1937, 2 folders (Box 72, Folder 13-14)
      - 1938-1939, 2 folders (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Greater New York Fund Inc, 1938; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Greyhound Corporation, 1931-1932; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Grocery Store Products, Printed, 1946; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Grosvenor Neighborhood House, 1930; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Guggenheim Fund, 1923-1942; 3 boxes
      - 1924-1928, 4 folders (Box 73, Folder 7-10)
      - 1928-1942, 5 folders (Box 74, Folder 1-5)
      - Printed, 1923-1929; 3 folders (Box 74, Folder 6-8)
      - Printed, 1930; 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
      - "Bulletin", 1926-1929; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Harmon Foundation, 1926-1927; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Harmon National Real Estate Corporation, 1926-1927; 1 box
      - 1926-1927, 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 5-6)
      - "Harmon Review", 1926; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Harper and Brothers, 1936; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Harvard University, 1924-1926; 1 box
      - 1924, 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Law School, 1926; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Henry Street Settlement House, 1916-1918; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Hospital Management Institute, 1929; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Hotchkiss School, "Hotchkiss Idea", 1924; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Hotel Pennysylvania, 1940; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad Company, 1920 March; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Hyde, James Hazen, 1920; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Hudson, River Tunnel, 1932; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - I.G. Farben-Industrie, Annual Report, 1934; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Industrial Relations Association, 1921; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Industrial Relations Counselors Inc, 1940; 1946; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1930; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Margarine Manufacturers, 1926; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Interborough Rapid Transit, 1916-1932; 3 boxes
      - 1921-1932, 4 folders (Box 76, Folder 13-16)
      - Presidents Communications, 1916-1919; 4 folders (Box 76, Folder 17-20)
      - (New York Street and Railways), 1920; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Printed Memorandum, 1918; 1925; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Annual Reports, 1917-1919; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - "Interborough Rapid Transit" #1-6, 1916-1918; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Printed, Labor Conferences, 1916; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Printed, Material Concerning Strikes, 1916; 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper Ads, 1916; 1918; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Printed Material by Theodore Shonts, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - "Interborough Bulletin", 1925; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Printed miscellaneous, 1923-1930; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Printed Material, Transit Commission, 1924; 1929; 1931; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Intercollegiate Treaty Referendum, 1919-1920; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - International Chamber of Commerce, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - International Machine Tool Corporation, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - International Salt, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - International Trader Conference, 1919; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Iodine Education Bureau, 1930-1931; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Italian American Society, 1921; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Jack and Heintz Precision Industries, 1946; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Jackson Brothers and Company, "Business", 1927-1928; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - J.P. Morgan and Company (French Bonds), 1920 September; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1922-1924; 2 boxes
      - 1922, 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - 1923-1924, 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
    - Joint Committee of Railroad and Highway Users, 1932; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Kahn, Otto H., 1916-1931; 2 boxes
      - 1917-1929, 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
      - Printed, 1916-1920; 3 folders (Box 79, Folder 6-8)
      - Printed, 1920-1931; 4 folders (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
    - Kansas and Gulf Company, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Kelly-Springfield Tire Company, 1936-1937; 2 folders (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
    - Kissel, Kinnicutt and Company (South American Investment), 1927; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Kosciuszko Foundation (Poland), 1928; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Kreuger and Toll, 1936; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Kuhn, Loeb and Company, 1945 September-October; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Ladenburg, Thalmann and Company (Piggly-Wiggly Stores), 1920; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Lawrence, John S, 1929; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Laymen's Inquiry into Foreign Missions, 1931; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, 1923-1925; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Lear Aviation Inc, 1944; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Higginson and Company, 1928; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Lenox Hill Neighborhood House Association, 1928; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Lever Brothers Company, 1919; 1945; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Liberty National Bank, 1920-1921; 1 box
      - 1920-1921, 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - "The Index", 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - "Present Day Scandinavia", 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Licensed Beverage Industries Inc., 1946; 2 boxes
      - 1946, 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 10-11)
      - Printed, 1946; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - "LBI News Letter", 1946; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Life Insurance Advertiser's Association, 1944 October; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Logan Country (W. VA) Coal Operators, 1921; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Luxford Taxicab Corporation, 1930; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Mackay Company, 1926-1928; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Magazine Repeating Razor Company, 1929; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Manufacturers Trust Company, 1931; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Mathewson, McLennan, and Molson, 1928; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Marine Studios, 1937-1939; 1 box
      - 1937-1939, 2 folders (Box 82, Folder 9-10)
      - Printed, 1937-1939; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Mason Builders Association, 1923; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Medical Funding Corporation, 1938; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Hospital, 1921; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Messenger, Willard Reed (Housing), 1923; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1934; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Square Company, 1929; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Squash Racquets Association, 1936-1940; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Trust, 1925; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Military Order of the World War, 1931-1932; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Muzak Inc, 1936; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Murray, 1942; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - N.A. Woodworth Company, 1942; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - National Air Transport, 1930; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - National Association of Broadcasters, 1941; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters, 1943-1946; 2 boxes
      - 1943-1945, 4 folders (Box 83, Folder 14-17)
      - 1945-1946, 2 folders (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed, 1943-1946; 2 folders (Box 84, Folder 3-4)
    - National Chain Store Associations, 1929; 1 box
      - 1929, 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1929; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - National Coal Associations, 1946 December; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - National Committee for America, 1917; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - National Dairy Products Company & Sheffield Farms Company, 1933-1934; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - National Dairy Producers Association Printed, 1933-1934; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - National Institute of Social Science, 1928; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - National Investors Corporation, 1936; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - The Navy Club, Manhattan, 1919; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Neptune Meter Company, 1927-1946; 1 box
      - (Water Works Research Bureau), 1927-1942; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1927-1946; 2 folders (Box 85, Folder 6-7)
    - Neurological Institute, 1931-1934; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - New England Council, 1928; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1923; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - New York Bar Association, 1929; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - New York City Defense Recreation Committee, 1944; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - The New York Hospital, 1945 November; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - New York Kindergarten Association, 1938- 1939; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - New York State Racing Commission, 1945 December; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - New York Railways Company, 1917-1918; 1 box
      - 1917-1918, 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Printed, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - New York Southern Society, 1923-1930; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - New York Title & Mortgage Company, 1927-1932; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - New York Trust Company, 1921-1946; 6 boxes
      - 1921-1931, 4 folders (Box 86, Folder 5-8)
      - 1932-1946, 3 folders (Box 87, Folder 1-3)
      - Printed, 1921-1943; 2 folders (Box 87, Folder 4-5)
      - "The Index", 1921-1946; 5 boxes
        - 1921-1922, 2 folders (Box 87, Folder 6-7)
        - 1923-1928, 6 folders (Box 88, Folder 1-6)
        - 1929-1934, 5 folders (Box 89, Folder 1-5)
        - 1934-1942, 7 folders (Box 90, Folder 1-7)
        - 1943-1946, 3 folders (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
    - Nickerson, John A, 1922; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Osborne, Edmund Jr, 1939; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Park Avenue Baptist Church, 1922-1928; 1 box
      - 1922-1928, 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Printed, 1923-1928; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Pension Fund of the Disciples of Christ, 1929; 1 folder (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1920-1947; 16 boxes
      - 1920-1921, 3 folders (Box 91, Folder 9-11)
      - 1921-1923, 6 folders (Box 92, Folder 1-6)
      - 1923-1926, 7 folders (Box 93, Folder 1-7)
      - 1926-1928, 6 folders (Box 94, Folder 1-6)
      - 1928-1929, 6 folders (Box 95, Folder 1-6)
      - 1930-1931, 6 folders (Box 96, Folder 1-6)
      - 1931-1933, 6 folders (Box 97, Folder 1-6)
      - 1933-1936, 6 folders (Box 98, Folder 1-6)
      - 1936-1940, 6 folders (Box 99, Folder 1-6)
      - 1940-1947, 4 folders (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
      - Annual Reports, 1923-1932; 2 folders (Box 100, Folder 5-6)
      - Annual Reports, 1934-1941; 2 folders (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
      - Speeches, 1921-1944; 4 folders (Box 101, Folder 3-6)